

### **Contact Me**

Aleppo,Sy

<u>+963-943581149</u>

My Portfolio

- M moahmmed.9issa@gmail.com
- **1.** t.me/m149i
- Inferno-Team
- in Mohammed Mousa AlEssa

## **Education**

2014-present
Aleppo University
Computer Engineering
5th academic year

## Mohammed Mousa Alissa

Senior Software Developer

#### **About Me**

I'm an experienced Android developer with 9+ years of experience, including 3 years in Laravel for backend development. My passion is creating high-quality, user-friendly applications across various industries. I excel in mobile app architecture, UI design, and performance optimization. I'm committed to innovation and staying updated with industry trends.

# **Work Experience**

FlexiAcademy | 01-05-2023 - Present BackEnd Laravel | Websocket

Inferno Team 10-10-2023 - Present

Owner Survey System

https://int.digiworlddev.com/participant/register/339b5d6ba84c161c2 51ba56b2349d50f

Women At Work | 21-07-2022 - Present Project Developer | My Day App

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=team.inferno.mobile.my\_day\_app&

Aleppo University | 2018-Present

Project Developer | Graduation Projects

all my projects are open sourced and you can find them on my github account

# **Expertise Skill**

- Android Studio
- VS Code
- Adobe XD
- Back4app

## Language Skill

- English
- Arabic



